universal-radio.com 2019-05-19

# Universal Radio Privacy Policy

**Table Of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**   
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Universal Radio website. On some pages, you can order products, send an email or request a catalog. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information   
(etc.) 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name   
Address   
Phone Number   
(etc.) 

**The Way We Use Information:**   
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties or other companies. The exception being a specific radio supplier for product support. For example, we may share your information with Icom if you buy an Icom radio. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties, except with specific suppliers for radio support. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you specifically request it. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We do not permanently store credit card information. This information is periodically purged. CID numbers are not stored electronically. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**   
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. There is no adult material on our website. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**   
You can verify your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by writing to Universal Radio. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**   
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact Mr. Osterman at 614 866-4267 or send an email to dx@universal-radio.com.
